In order to calculate the answer to this question,
为了计算出这个问题的答案
instead of doing it by hand, I'm going to let Python do the work.
我不用手写计算 我要让 Python 做这项工作
What I've done is I've collected together the data from the question,
我做的事是从问题中收集数据
the total time of the round trip for the data, which was 75 milliseconds,
数据往返的总时间：75 毫秒
the one-way distance, which was 2,500 kilometers, the speed of light in an optic fiber,
单程距离是 2,500 千米
which is 200,000 km/sec.
光在光纤的速度是每秒 200,000 千米
Note that this is kilometers per second, but the total time is in milliseconds,
请注意这是 千米/秒 但总时间是以毫秒为单位
which means I'm going to need a conversion between milliseconds and seconds.
也就是说 我需要在毫秒和秒之间做转换
Let's think. What do I need to calculate?
让我们想一下 执行计算时需要什么？
Well, what I want to know is the totaltimeat_routers.
嗯 我想知道 total_time_at_routers
Working backwards from what I want to know, let's see what I need to calculate.
从我想知道的点做回溯 让我们想想执行计算时需要什么
Well, the total time spent at the routers is equal to the total_time minus the timeonthe_wires.
嗯 在路由器上花费的总时间等于 total_time 减去 time_on_the_wires
How am I going to calculate the timeonthe_wires?
我要如何计算 time_on_the_wires 呢?
That's while it's in the fiber optics rather than actually at the routers.
这是它在光纤花的时间 而不是真的在路由器上 (router)
The time on the wires--that's equal to--well, how do we calculate time
在光纤上的时间 是等于
when we've got distances and speed?
当我们得到距离和速度 如何计算出时间的方法
Well, it's simply distance divided by speed.
嗯 它只是距离除以速度
Now, what distance are we using?
现在 我们使用的距离是什么？
Well, the total timeatthe_routers is equal to total_time.
嗯 总时间 total_time_at_routers 等于 total_time
That's actually the time for the round trip, so we need to know how long the data
这是实际的往返时间 所以我们需要知道
was on the fiber optics for the round trip, which means we need to go twice the distance.
在往返行程里 数据在光纤中走了多远的距离 这意味着 我们需将距离乘以两倍
That's the one-way distance.
这是单向的距离
We're going to divide by the speed that the data is traveling in the wires,
我们要除以速度 这是数据在光纤上传输的速度
which is the optical speed.
是光的速度
Now at the moment, we've got--what have we got here?
现在 我们得到了什么？
We've got kilometers divided by km/sec, which is going to give us an answer in seconds.
我们得到 km 除以 km/s 答案是以秒为单位
But our times are measured in milliseconds, so that's seconds at the moment,
但我们的时间是以毫秒为单位 这里是秒
and we want to convert it into milliseconds.
我们要将它转换成毫秒
We have to multiply it by the number of milliseconds per second.
我们要将它乘以每秒的毫秒数
That's our conversion factor, which is milliseconds per second.
这是我们的换算系数 即每秒的毫秒数
Let's see what happens--75.
让我们看看结果 — 75
That's a bit weird, isn't it? Because the total time was 75.
这有点怪 不是吗? 因为总时间是 75
What's gone wrong?
哪里错了?
Let me just print out here the timeonthe_wires--0.
我在这里印出 time_on_the_wires 为 0
Well, that doesn't make sense, does it?
嗯 这不合理 不是吗?
Because it's been somewhere, and it's come back--it can't have taken 0 time.
因为它曾在某个地方 现在已经回来了 它不可能花的时间是 0
What's the problem here?
问题是什么?
Well, the problem is this division.
嗯 问题是除法
What we have in Python--at least before version 3--is that division is integer division.
我们在 Python 至少在版本 3 之前  除法是整数除法
So if the number is less than 1, which it will be here,
所以如果数目小于 1 在这里
because onewaydistance is only 2,500, and we're dividing by 200,000.
因为 one_way_distance 仅为 2500 而我们要除以 200,000
Python just rounds it down to the nearest integer, which is 0.
Python 只是将它做四舍五入到最接近的整数 也就是 0
In order to deal with that, I'm just going to make it into a float,
为了处理这个情况 我把它改为浮点数 (float)
which means that it does division normally and gives an answer which is a decimal.
这意味着它做正常的除法 给的答案是有小数点的
You can convert all of these into floats, but really we just need to do one of them.
你可以将这些都转换为浮点数 (floats)  但实际上 我们只需改掉其中一个
If I run it now, I find that the first value here--25--is the amount of time on the wires,
如果我现在执行它 我发现的第一个值在这里 25 在光纤上的时间
and the totaltimeat_routers is 50 milliseconds.
total_time_at_routers 为 50 毫秒
You need to be a little bit careful to make sure that you're doing float division.
你需要小心一点 以确定你做了浮点除法 (float division)
Float is just decimal division instead of integer division.
浮点 (float) 不是整数除法 而是小数除法